A Guide to the University of Virginia Dean of the Curry School of Education Office Administrative Files, 1970-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Off-Grounds Programs
  - Tidewater Consortium, 1975 (Folder 28)
  - Valley Consortium Meetings, 1975 (Folder 28)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1980-1981 (Folder 28)
  - Wise County- Administration and Supervision, n.d. (Folder 28)
- Correspondence
  - General Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 January (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 February (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence (2 folders), 1976 March (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 April (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 May (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 July (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 August (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 September (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 October (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 January (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 February (Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 March (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 April (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 May (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 June (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 July (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 August (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 September (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 October (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 November (Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 December (Folder 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1974
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1975 (Folder 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1976 (Folder 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence (2 folders), 1977 (Folder 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence (2 folders), 1978 January/October (Folder 31)
  - Personal Correspondence- Richard Brandt, 1975 (Folder 31)
  - Personal Correspondence- Richard Brandt, 1976 (Folder 31)
  - Personal Correspondence- Richard Brandt, 1977 (Folder 31)
  - Personal Correspondence- Richard Brandt, 1978 (Folder 31)
  - Correspondence- Fowler to Brandt, 1974-1975 (Folder 31)
  - Correspondence- Brandt to Fowler, 1975 (Folder 31)
  - Correspondence- Adelle Robertson, 1981 (Folder 31)
  - Correspondence- to Brandt and Shannon, 1976 (Folder 31)
  - Correspondence and Notes- B. W. Nelson, 1975 (Folder 31)
  - Early Correspondence- Drug Abuse, 1975 (Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Folder 32)
  - Medical School Correspondence, prior 1981 (Folder 32)